LANCE**MCFEE**

Customer Support Engineer

work experience

Oracle Cerner Healthcare IT System Support Analyst | 2022-present

- Providing remote support for medical record software and bedside medical device connectivity.
- First point of contact for clinical staff working under the umbrella of the Immediate Response Center.
- Daily client-facing interaction over the phone to help resolve critical production issues.
- Ran MySQL queries and Cerner's proprietary command line (CCL) on linux servers to troubleshoot medical devices.
- Familiar with RDP connecting to citrix farms and ssh to Linux app nodes for basic software troubleshooting.
- Utilized a ticketing system to track incidents and collaborate with other support teams.
- Worked in accordance with Immediate Response Center to help engage tier 2 or tier 3 resources.

Cerner Inc. Healthcare IT System Engineer | 2015-2021

- Manage multi-tenant domains in Production and Mock domains.
- Charged with creating backend Linux user accounts, modifying permissions, building network printers, or troubleshooting SSH/SFTP.
- Execute weekly and monthly package deployments and manage quarterly major code releases.
- Projects include: App-Tier Linux migrations, RHEL upgrades / migrations, and WebSphere on Linux Upgrades, and troubleshooting any issues after their Go-Live events.

LM Photography, Kansas City, MO Freelance photographer | 2015-2020

- Portrait Photography
- Contract photography for on-site advertisements

ISPN | Technical Support Level Field Technician | 2014-2015

- Installing cable internet and TV services
- Assigned to domestic and commercial locations

nicklancemcfee@gmail.com 816-560-6259 216 w. 51st Terrace Floor 2 Kansas City, MO 64112

statement

IT professional with a formal background in system administration as well as commercial photography. Has 7 years' experience configuring enterprise servers while developing web design skills that coencide with photography related websites on the side. Enjoys interacting with clients to provide quick resolution to software issues.

education

University of Central Missouri | 2006-2009 Bachelors of Science and Technology Commercial Photography

Devry University | 2014-2015 | Dean's List 3.4 GPA Associates of Applied Science Network System Administration

software

Adobe Photoshop & Lightroom | Revit, AutoCad Adobe Illustrator & Indesign | Logos and Layouts Adobe Premier | Video Editing Semrush | SEO keyword and backlink research Wordpress CMS - | WP core, WP-cli, phpmyadmin VScode | debugging html, css, javascript, php

certifications

SEO Training for Wordpress Websites Udemy 2023 |

Logo Design Mastery in Adobe Illustrator Udemy 2022 |

Wordpress Developer: Unlocking Power with Code Udemy 2022 |